#### Contact

mikhail.bolshakov@hotmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/mikhail-bolshakov-08165a18b (LinkedIn) mikhail-bolshakov.github.io/cv/index.html (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Data Analysis Business Intelligence (BI) Python (Programming Language)

## Languages

English (Professional Working)
German (Elementary)
Russian (Native or Bilingual)

#### Certifications

Google Analytics for Beginners
Python Programming
Data Analytics - Mining and Analysis
of Big Data

Modernizing Data Lakes and Data Warehouses with Google Cloud Platform

Python for Data Science and Al

# Mikhail Bolshakov

Business Intelligence | Data Analyst at DrSmile Berlin

# Summary

Curious and passionate BI Analyst with 2+ years of hands-on experience in different stages of data analysis.

Have a strong scientific background in quantitative analysis and research, problem-solving skills coupled with an analytical mindset, affinity for technology and a keen interest for learning new technical concepts.

### Competencies:

ELT/ETL, Data Warehousing, Dimensional Modeling, Data Analytics, Data Visualization.

Tech Stack:

Postgres, Snowflake, Python, dbt, Airflow, Power BI, Looker.

# Experience

DrSmile
Data Analyst
January 2021 - Present (5 months)
Berlin, Germany

#### LIEFERY

Business Intelligence Developer October 2020 - January 2021 (4 months)

Berlin, Berlin, Germany

bookingkit

2 years 1 month

Business Intelligence Manager February 2020 - October 2020 (9 months)

Berlin, Germany

Junior Business Intelligence Manager October 2018 - February 2020 (1 year 5 months)

Berlin Area, Germany

Brandenburgische Technische Universität Cottbus-Senftenberg Wissenschaftliche Hilfskraft

June 2018 - August 2018 (3 months)

Cottbus, Brandenburg

Russia Banquet Hall
Event Coordinator
August 2013 - September 2014 (1 year 2 months)
Cheboksary, Chuvashia, Russia

Marketing, planning and coordinating of all aspects of private events.

Responsible for

generating a sales and marketing plan to achieve departmental revenue goals

### Education

Brandenburgische Technische Universität Cottbus-Senftenberg Master of Science - MS, Environmental and Resource Management · (2015 - 2019)

Brandenburgische Technische Universität Cottbus-Senftenberg Unfinished, World Heritage Studies · (2014 - 2015)

Saint Petersburg State University of Engineering and Economics Master's degree, Hospitality Administration/Management · (2003 - 2008)